vaughns-1-pagers.com 2011-11-01

# Privacy Policy - Vaughn's Summaries

. **  
Privacy Policy - Vaughn's Summaries**  
  
**1\. I collect NO data.**

| 

No need to "Opt-Out". I don't want your email address, or other personal information. No SPAM from me, ever.  
  
**2\. No Cookies**

| 

I do not spy on your behavior using cookies - you will never be tracked by me. My web host does use a cookie, but this is for server log purposes only.  
  
**3\. Web Log Files**

| 

I don't care what your IP Address is. (The one exception to this is if I am attacked, in which case your IP and other associated information will be of great interest to my associates.)  
  
**4\. Google Ads**

| 

This site does not collect any data from visitors, other than standard server logs. However, this site does serve ads from Google, who does collect data from visitors, when the ads are clicked upon. See the Google Privacy Policy at [http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html](http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html) for the data that may be collected, and what it might be used for.  
  
**5\. DoubleClick DART cookie**

| 

* Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site.  
* Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to this site and other sites on the Internet.  
* Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).   
  
\- 

| 

That's it. Have you seen a shorter Privacy Policy?  
An Exception - Indirect Tracking \- Certain subtle information on this web site is intentionally misstated. This helps me to identify those who steal my content, or intentionally cause me to have other problems.

The longer the "Privacy Policy", the more you should worry.  
Typical privacy policies run about 1,500 to 4,000 words.  
My privacy policy is quite short - 336 words.
